

## **ABOUT**

Hello! My name is Bavo Devos, I am a game programmer at Filimundus, equipped with C++ and C# with hands on experience working with Unity, Unreal and Custom Engines. In my free time I enjoy developing VR games and playing games, my favorite genre being Grand Strategy.

## **SKILLS**

- C++
- C#
- HTML
- CSS
- LUA
- Unity
- Unreal
- SDL
- Git
- Perforce

## CONTACT

Stockholm, Sweden bavo.devos21@gmail.com +32 479 70 86 95

github.com/BavoDevos linkedin.com/in/bavodevos Portfolio Website

# BAVO DEVOS

# **GAME PROGRAMMER**

## **EDUCATION**

Howest, Digital Arts & Entertainment | Belgium, Kortrijk

Bachelor Game Development | 2021-2024

During my education at Howest I have acquired a strong foundation in C++ and C#, developed my knowledge about gameplay programming, engine programming and graphics programming and additionally game design.

## **EXPERIENCE**

August 2024 - Current

Filimundus AB | Game Programmer | Stockholm

Taking ownership and developing an NDA project as well as maintaining older games and applications.

February 2024 - June 2024

Filimundus AB | Game Programmer Intern | Stockholm

Taking ownership and developing Pettson's Inventions 4 as well as being the Platform Manager, maintaining older games.

## **LANGUAGES**

English | Native Dutch | Native French | Beginner